MAN WING FAI

Rm2804, Ching Chak House, Ching Ho Estate

Sheung Shui, New Territories, Hong Kong

Website: manfai.me

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/wingfai-man

manfai106@gmail.com | 93517034

INTRODUCTION

In my current job at a Co-Dining Platform. I have worked on the front-end, back-end part. At the beginning, I was asked to build a big system for user order bento and pick-up it on a vending machine. I need to complete this system in 6 month. It was a challenge because I had never created a big system like this. It's not only a website, app or backend. It's a skill on IoT. But it was a good chance because I had experience with creating these systems in few of my previous jobs, so it was a great chance to show my skills.

EDUCATION

Coventry University

BSc (Hons) Multimedia Computing, 2015 - 2016

Institute of Vocational Education (Sha Tin)

Higher Diploma in Multimedia, 2013 - 2015

Institute of Vocational Education (Sha Tin)

Foundation Diploma (Level3) in Computing, 2012 - 2013

WORK EXPERIENCE

ECBento HK Ltd.

Developer, 2019 - 2020

Design and Develop Vending Machine System + Back-end System + Front-end System

Design and Develop API + API Document

Maintenance web server (Alibaba / AWS)

Virtual Sport Ltd.

Freelance Developer, 2018 - 2020

Design and Develop Back-end System + Front-end System

Design and Develop API + API Document

Maintenance web server (Alibaba / AWS / Godaddy)

HKICTech Ltd.

Senior Web Programmer, 2017 - 2019

Design and Develop websites to clients

Maintenance web server (Nginx + CentOS)

Freelance

Freelance Web Programmer, 2015 - 2016

Design and Develop a few Wordpress websites

http://hkfcpro.com, http://focuslearning.com.hk, http://www.iilhk.com

Speedy Group Corporation Limited

Technical Support Assistant, 2015 - 2016

IT support for Shung Tak Catholic English College

Wise Smart Strategy Limited

Internship Trainee, Summer 2014

Develop a website for Wise Smart Strategy Limited

COMPETITION

Pan-Pearl River Delta Region University IT Project Competition 2015

Silver medal

Hong Kong ICT Award 2016

Participant

TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE

Projects

ECBento - A Food-Locker platform (Front-end & Back-end & APP)

https://ecbento.com

https://apps.apple.com/hk/app/ec-bento/id1529050746?l=en

Freelance Projects

VRace24 - A virtual sport platform (Front-end & Back-end)

https://vrace24.com

Company Official Website (Front-end)

http://www.ngc-knowledge.com

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages:

PHP, JQuery, Nodejs, HTML, CSS, XML, MySQL, Ajax, JavaScript, Python, Swift, Objective-c, Vuejs

Framework:

Laravel, Laravel Nova, Codeigniter

Tools:

Xcode, Android Studio, PyCharm, Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, Visual Studio, Adobe Premiere Pro, Final Cut Pro

Operating systems:

Windows, Ubuntu, macOS.